What will you have?
‫ماذا ستطلب؟‬
The usual.
‫المعتاد.‬
Your usual? I forgot what that is.
‫طلبك المعتاد؟ نسيته.‬
When are you going to remember, Robbie?
‫متى ستتذكره يا "روبي"؟‬
Hamburger, double cheese, extra ketchup, thick-sliced tomatoes.
‫شطيرة برغر بقطعتي جبن‬ ‫وصلصة طماطم إضافية وشرائح طماطم سميكة.‬
Slip in pickles, and you're dead.
‫إن وضعت مخللًا، فسأجهز عليك.‬
You expect me to remember that?
‫أتتوقع مني أن أتذكر ذلك؟‬
That Chinese or Vietnamese dude, he's been nosing around about you.
‫ثمة شخص صيني أو فيتنامي يتحرّى عنك.‬
He comes here a lot lately.
‫يأتي إلى كثيرًا مؤخرًا.‬
He even asked me who you were.
‫بل وسألني عمّن تكون.‬
He's no Chinese or Vietnamese dude.
‫إنه ليس صينيًا ولا فيتناميًا.‬
Really?
‫حقًا؟‬
I'm pretty sure he's Japanese.
‫أنا متأكد من أنه ياباني.‬
He's a neurosurgeon, and a damn fine one too.
‫إنه جرّاح مخ وأعصاب وبارع أيضًا.‬
Isn't that right, Dr. Tenma?
‫أليس كذلك يا د. "تينما"؟‬
Answer me!
‫أجبني!‬
Your ex-fiancée was the daughter of the director of your hospital.
‫خطيبتك السابقة كانت ابنة مدير المستشفى.‬
What are you going to do to Eva?
‫ما الذي ستفعله بـ"إيفا"؟‬
"Eva"?
‫"إيفا"؟‬
It's "Ms. Heinemann" to you, pal! You ain't engaged to her anymore.
‫اسمها السيدة "هاينمان" يا صاح!‬ ‫لم تعد خطيبتك.‬
Not only are you not a doctor anymore but you're also a fugitive.
‫لم تعد طبيبًا فحسب،‬ ‫بل وإنك هارب من العدالة.‬
Go to prison, serve your time and start over.
‫سلّم نفسك واقض مدة حبسك وابدأ من جديد.‬
If you're a model inmate, you could even get out early.
‫إن أصبحت سجينًا حسن السلوك،‬ ‫فقد تخرج قبل إنهاء مدتك.‬
Let Eva go!
‫أطلق سراح "إيفا"!‬
Let her go?
‫أطلق سراحها؟‬
I ain't holding her against her will.
‫أنا لا أحتجزها.‬
She's going to parties every day.
‫إنها تحضر الحفلات يوميًا.‬
Let me see Eva!
‫دعني أرى "إيفا"!‬
Let you see her?
‫أدعك تراها؟‬
Hey! Don't go trashing my place.
‫إياك أن تحطّم مطعمي.‬
Quit hanging around here. Now get lost.
‫ابتعد عن المكان هنا. والآن اغرب عن وجهي.‬
Eva…
‫"إيفا"…‬
Get lost.
‫اغرب عن هنا.‬
Did you see Kenzo?
‫رأيت "كينزو"؟‬
Yes, a couple of days ago.
‫نعم، قبل يومين.‬
I thought I should at least tell you.
‫ارتأيت أنه يجدر بي أن أخبرك على الأقل.‬
He wants to see you.
‫يريد رؤيتك.‬
You didn't beat him up, did you?
‫أنت لم تضربه، أليس كذلك؟‬
No. I wouldn't do that.
‫لا. ما كنت لأفعل ذلك.‬
-We're leaving. -Huh?
‫- سنغادر.‬ ‫- ماذا؟‬
You're done with today's party already?
‫اكتفيت بحفلة واحدة اليوم؟‬
Not just for today. I'm done with parties.
‫ليس لهذا اليوم فحسب. فرغت منها مطلقًا.‬
Probably.
‫على الأرجح.‬
Well done, Eva.
‫أحسنت يا "إيفا".‬
How about having dinner with me?
‫ما رأيك في تناول العشاء معي؟‬
Sure.
‫موافقة طبعًا.‬
So, you dropped her off at some restaurant,
‫أوصلتها إلى مطعم،‬
but you came here for dinner?
‫وأتيت إلى هنا لتناول العشاء؟‬
Compared to the food at those parties and high-class restaurants,
‫مقارنة بطعام تلك الحفلات والمطاعم الراقية،‬
the hamburgers here are way better.
‫فإن شطيرة البرغر هذه أشهى بكثير.‬
I'm not sure if that's a compliment or an insult.
‫لست متأكدًا ممّا إن كان هذا مديحًا أم ذمًّا.‬
You're getting annoying.
‫بدأت تصبح مزعجًا.‬
Do you want to get hurt again?
‫أتريد التعرّض للأذى مجددًا؟‬
I thought I told you to get--
‫حسبتني أمرتك…‬
You behind the counter, freeze!
‫اثبت يا من خلف المنضدة.‬
Move and I'll shoot.
‫سأطلق النار إن تحرّكت.‬
We've got a dangerous doctor here.
‫ثمة طبيب خطر هنا.‬
Who hired you?
‫من استأجرك؟‬
I know your boss is The Baby.
‫أعرف أن زعيمك هو "ذا بيبي".‬
But the man who ordered you to protect Eva
‫لكن من أمرك بحماية "إيفا"‬
is even higher up in the organization.
‫أعلى منصبًا منه في المنظمة.‬
Who gave you your orders?
‫من أمرك؟‬
I don't know who he is.
‫لا أعرف من يكون.‬
But I know what he looks like.
‫لكنني أعرف شكله.‬
He's a man with glasses.
‫إنه رجل يرتدي نظّارة.‬
A man with glasses?
‫يرتدي نظّارة؟‬
What is he making Eva do?
‫بم يكلّف "إيفا"؟‬
Like I told you, he's just having Eva go to parties.
‫كما أخبرتك، كلّفها بحضور الحفلات.‬
She eats, drinks then leaves. That's all.
‫تشرب وتأكل ومن ثم تغادر. فقط لا غير.‬
That can't be all!
‫لا يُعقل أن هذا هو المطلوب فحسب!‬
She must be doing something special at those parties!
‫من المؤكد أن ثمة أمر خارج عن المألوف‬ ‫تفعله في تلك الحفلات!‬
No.
‫لا.‬
-Come to think of it, today… -Today?
‫- عند التفكير في ذلك، فاليوم…‬ ‫- اليوم؟‬
Never mind, it was nothing.
‫لا عليك، ليس بأمر جلل.‬
She pointed at someone.
‫أشارت إلى شخص ما.‬
She pointed at someone?
‫أشارت إلى شخص؟‬
A young man.
‫شاب.‬
A young man?
‫شاب؟‬
She went like this…
‫فعلت هذا…‬
and pointed at a young blonde man with a pretty face.
‫وأشارت إلى شاب أشقر وسيم الوجه.‬
But that was all.
‫لكن هذا كلّ ما حدث.‬
Where's Eva now?
‫أين "إيفا" الآن؟‬
She's having dinner with that guy with glasses who hired me.
‫تتناول العشاء مع من يرتدي النظّارة‬ ‫الذي استأجرني.‬
Where? Tell me now! Where are they?
‫أين؟ أخبرني في الحال! أين هما؟‬
Eva's job is over now!
‫انتهت مهمة "إيفا"!‬
When this job is over, I'm sure I'll be murdered.
‫أنا متأكدة من أنني سأُقتل‬ ‫بعد الانتهاء من هذه المهمة.‬
I'm done with parties.
‫فرغت من الحفلات.‬
Where is Eva?
‫أين "إيفا"؟‬
Stop!
‫توقف!‬
Where is she?
‫أين هي؟‬
I sent her to her hotel.
‫أرسلتها إلى الفندق.‬
Do you have a gun?
‫هل معك مسدس؟‬
No… I never carry a gun.
‫لا، لا أحمل مسدسًا.‬
Then use this one.
‫استخدم هذا إذًا.‬
Kill her.
‫اقتلها.‬
That night, the party was just like all the other ones we went to.
‫في تلك الليلة،‬ ‫كانت الحفلة غيرها من الحفلات التي حضرناها.‬
The smell of liquor.
‫رائحة الخمر.‬
The smell of perfume.
‫رائحة العطر.‬
Empty laughter.
‫الضحكات المصطنعة.‬
It was the same as always.
‫كما كان الحال دائمًا.‬
Except for that single moment.
‫عدا تلك اللحظة.‬
Eva pointed at a certain young man.
‫أشارت "إيفا" إلى شاب.‬
Then the man with glasses showed up with another well-dressed young man.
‫ثم ظهر من يرتدي النظّارة مع رجل آخر متأنّق.‬
Then the two young men shook hands.
‫ثم تصافح الشابين.‬
I didn't notice it at the time, but that was when Eva's job ended.
‫لم ألاحظ ذلك آنذاك،‬ ‫لكن مهمة "إيفا" كانت قد انتهت بذلك.‬
I figured it would be you who would kill me.
‫عرفت أنك من ستقتلني.‬
Go right ahead.
‫اقتلني.‬
I've already gotten pretty drunk.
‫أنا قد ثملت تمامًا.‬
I've got no more regrets either.
‫كما أنني ما عدت أشعر بالندم.‬
That's right.
‫هذا صحيح.‬
You can't shoot me at this hotel, can you?
‫لا يمكنك أن تطلق عليّ النار في الفندق هنا.‬
You told me how when you shot your girlfriend,
‫وصفت لي اللحظة‬ ‫التي أطلقت فيها النار على حبيبتك‬
you found yourself standing in a sea of blood.
‫وأنك وجدت نفسك في بركة من الدماء.‬
Take me outside when you shoot me.
‫اصطحبني إلى الخارج وأطلق عليّ النار.‬
If you don't, they'll make you pay to clean the room.
‫إن لم تفعل، فسيحمّلونك تكلفة تنظيف الغرفة.‬
There is still one thing that I regret.
‫ثمة ما أندم عليه.‬
Although, I guess it doesn't matter.
‫مع أن ما من أهمية لذلك.‬
Why the hell did I do that today anyway?
‫لم أقدمت على فعل ذلك اليوم؟‬
You saw me, right? When I pointed.
‫رأيتني، صحيح؟ عندما أشرت بإصبعي.‬
I bet what I did today was pretty damn terrible.
‫أنا متأكدة من أن ما فعلته اليوم‬ ‫كان أمرًا فظيعًا.‬
I brought together some horrible people with the devil.
‫ساهمت في التقاء عددًا من الأشخاص المرّوعين‬ ‫مع الشيطان.‬
Like bringing together Mephistopheles and Faust.
‫كأن تساهم‬ ‫في التقاء "مفيستوفيليس" بـ"فاوست".‬
But who cares anyway?
‫لكن من يأبه؟‬
After what I did today, I won't be going to any more parties.
‫بعد ما فعلته اليوم،‬ ‫لن أحضر المزيد من الحفلات.‬
But I've still got all these invitations to parties that are coming up.
‫لكن لا يزال معي كل تلك الدعوات‬ ‫لحفلات مقبلة.‬
If you'd like
‫إن أردت،‬
when I'm dead, why don't you check up on what I did?
‫من بعد موتي، لما لا تتفقد نتاج ما فعلته؟‬
All right, you may as well put an end to this.
‫حسنًا، يمكنك حسم تلك المسألة.‬
Run away.
‫اهربي.‬
Run away with me.
‫اهربي معي.‬
I think you've got me all wrong.
‫أظن أنك أسأت فهمي.‬
Run away with you? You can't be serious!
‫أهرب معك؟ لا يمكن أن تكون جادًا.‬
When did we get so close?
‫متى توطدت علاقتنا؟‬
I can't…
‫ما عدت…‬
I can't kill people anymore.
‫ما عدت قادرًا على قتل الناس.‬
You can't kill people? But could you kill a devil?
‫ليس باستطاعتك قتل الناس؟ ‬ ‫لكن يمكنك قتل شيطان؟‬
I'm a devil.
‫أنا شيطانة.‬
That suit and necktie that I bought for you,
‫تلك البدلة وربطة العنق‬ ‫اللاتي اشتريتهما لك،‬
they're the same ones Kenzo wore long ago.
‫هما ما ارتداهما "كينزو" فيما سبق منذ زمن.‬
Don't you get it? I dressed you up to look like Kenzo Tenma.
‫ألا تفهم؟‬ ‫ألبستك ما كان يلبسه "كينزو تينما".‬
Kill me!
‫اقتلني!‬
Hurry up and kill me!
‫أسرع واقتلني.‬
Do it now!
‫افعل هذا الآن!‬
Unless you kill me soon…
‫إن لم تقتلني عاجلًا…‬
then you'll be killed.
‫فسأُقتل.‬
I could kill a devil, huh?
‫يمكنني قتل شيطان؟‬
Mom, wake up!
‫أفيقي يا أمي؟‬
I'll be just fine.
‫سأكون بخير.‬
I just need to sleep this off for a bit.
‫أريد النوم فقط لتخفيف حدة ما أنا فيه.‬
You can't! You'll die if you fall asleep here!
‫لا مجال لذلك! ستموتين إن نمت هنا!‬
I'll be fine. Just leave me here a bit.
‫سأكون بخير. اتركني هنا فحسب لبعض الوقت.‬
You sure look gloomy.
‫يبدو الاكتئاب واضحًا عليك.‬
I always look gloomy.
‫دائمًا ما أكون كذلك.‬
Did anyone come looking for me?
‫هل أتى أحدهم بحثًا عني؟‬
No, not a soul.
‫لا أحد مطلقًا.‬
But that Japanese guy left this with me last night.
‫لكن ذلك الياباني ترك لي هذا ليلة أمس.‬
"Hellblau Hotel Room 205."
‫"فندق (هيبلاو)، غرفة 205."‬
He said to contact him there if you need anything.
‫قال تواصل معه في حال أردت شيئًا.‬
Do you want your usual?
‫أتريد طلبك المعتاد؟‬
No thanks.
‫لا، شكرًا.‬
If I fill up on some disgusting hamburger, I'll lose the will to go.
‫إن أخذت آكل شطيرة برغر مقززة،‬ ‫فلن أكون مقبلًا على الذهاب.‬
Go where?
‫إلى أين؟‬
A party.
‫حفلة.‬
It's crazy, ain't it?
‫إنه لأمر لا يُصدق.‬
With just a single necktie, they'll let you in anywhere.
‫يُسمح للمرء بالدخول بسبب ربطة عنق.‬
Just one of these…
‫بواحدة من ربطات العنق هذه…‬
There he is.
‫وجدته.‬
So, that guy's a devil, huh?
‫ذلك الرجل هو الشيطان إذًا؟‬
He shook hands with so many people that his hand must be rubbed raw.
‫صافح الكثير من الناس‬ ‫إلى درجة أن يده كادت تنسلخ.‬
Then he left the party venue.
‫ثم غادر الحفلة.‬
The sixth floor, eh?
‫الطابق السادس؟‬
But which room is he in?
‫ولكن في أي غرفة هو؟‬
Please go inside.
‫تفضل بالدخول من فضلك.‬
Please take a seat here.
‫تفضل بالجلوس هنا.‬
Make yourself comfortable.
‫خذ راحتك.‬
You want to meet him too, don't you?
‫تريد أن تقابله أنت أيضًا، أليس كذلك؟‬
"Him"?
‫أقابله؟‬
I'm waiting for him too. He'll be here soon.
‫أنا أنتظره أيضًا. سيأتي إلى هنا بعد قليل.‬
Let's talk a little until he arrives. Let's see, what should we talk about?
‫لنتحدّث إلى أن يصل. عمّ يجب أن نتحدّث؟‬
I know.
‫أعرف.‬
Let's talk about the end of the world.
‫لنتحدّث عن نهاية العالم.‬
The young punk happily blabbered on.
‫أخذ الشاب التافه يثرثر مبتهجًا.‬
He talked like a child speaking to his parents
‫أخذ يتحدّث كما لو أنه يخاطب والديه‬
about the fun he had at school that day.
‫عن ما شعر به من متعة في مدرسته ذاك اليوم.‬
He just kept talking to me like that.
‫استمر في التحدّث إليّ على هذا النحو.‬
"The end of the world," my ass.
‫سحقًا لنهاية العالم.‬
The crazy young punk's talk was a bunch of nonsense.
‫حديث الشاب التافه المعتل كان مجرد هراء.‬
That's what I thought at the time.
‫ذلك ما حسبته آنذاك.‬
What did you think? Pretty interesting, isn't it?
‫ما رأيك؟ إنه لأمر مثير للغاية، أليس كذلك؟‬
Did you enjoy it, Martin?
‫هل استمتعت بكلامي يا "مارتن"؟‬
How come you know my name?
‫كيف تعرف اسمي؟‬
Here's an idea. Let's talk about you next.
‫إليك هذه الفكرة. لنتحدّث عنك تاليًا.‬
You've been working for The Baby for three years now.
‫مضى على عملك مع "ذا بيبي" ثلاث سنوات.‬
Have you been looking into me?
‫هل كنت تتحرّى عني؟‬
Before that, you were in prison.
‫قبل ذلك، كنت في السجن.‬
Those must have been a hard eight years.
‫لا بد أن الثماني سنوات تلك كانت عصيبة.‬
You were a model inmate though, right?
‫كنت سجينًا حسن السلوك، أليس كذلك؟‬
You got out pretty quickly for having been a murderer.
‫مع أنها جريمة قتل إلا أنك خرجت سريعًا.‬
Did you enjoy living with your girlfriend?
‫هل استمتعت بحياتك مع حبيبتك؟‬
You know, the girlfriend you shot and killed. Her name was Edda.
‫حبيبتك من أطلقت عليها النار وقتلتها.‬ ‫اسمها كان "إيدا".‬
You've got pretty poor taste, pal.
‫أرى أنك عديم الذوق يا رجل.‬
She was a total drug addict, wasn't she?
‫كانت مدمنة تمامًا على تعاطي المخدرات.‬ ‫ألم تكن كذلك؟‬
You did everything you could to get her off drugs.
‫فعلت كلّ ما بوسعك لتخليصها من التعاطي.‬
That's not easy to do.
‫ليس من السهل فعل ذلك.‬
I guess you did it out of love.
‫أظن أنك فعلت هذا بسبب حبك لها.‬
Do you want to get hurt?
‫أتريد أن تتعرّض للأذى؟‬
She got back on her feet.
‫استعادت صحتها.‬
She'd make you dinner and wait for you to come home.
‫كانت تعدّ لك العشاء وتنتظر عودتك إلى البيت.‬
You started living a happy life together.
‫بدأتما تعيشان معًا حياة سعيدة.‬
Do you want me to punch your lights out?
‫أتريدني أن أبرحك ضربًا؟‬
But one night, when you got home, you saw something that blew your mind.
‫ولكن في ليلة ما، عندما عدت إلى بيتك،‬ ‫رأيت ما أذهلك.‬
Her ex-boyfriend was at your place.
‫حبيبها السابق كان في بيتك.‬
She'd done drugs again,
‫تعاطت مجددًا،‬
and while in a daze, she said to you over and over again,
‫وفي حالة من الذهول،‬ ‫أخذت تقول مرارًا وتكرارًا،‬
"I'm sorry."
‫"أنا آسفة."‬
But you shot and killed both her and the man.
‫لكنك أطلقت عليها النار هي والرجل وقتلتهما.‬
At least that's how it came out in court.
‫هذا ما قيل في المحكمة على الأقل.‬
Why did you lie?
‫لم كذبت؟‬
She killed herself, right?
‫هي من قتلت نفسها، أليس كذلك؟‬
Since she had gunshot residue on her hand,
‫نظرًا لأنه كان في يدها بقايا من طلق ناري،‬
your lawyer figured she had killed herself.
‫أدرك محاميك أنها انتحرت.‬
However, you insisted that you had shot her.
‫مع ذلك أخذت تصرّ‬ ‫على أنك من أطلقت عليها النار.‬
She asked you to kill her, didn't she?
‫طلبت منك أن تقتلها، أليس كذلك؟‬
Bullseye! I'm right, aren't I?
‫أصبت كبد الحقيقة. أنا محق، صحيح؟‬
I knew it. It wasn't you who shot her, was it?
‫كنت أعرف. لم تكن من أطلق النار عليها.‬
I bet this is what she said, "Shoot me."
‫أنا متأكد من أن هذا ما قالته،‬ ‫"أطلق عليّ النار."‬
Shoot me.
‫أطلق عليّ النار.‬
Don't look at me like that!
‫لا ترمقني بتلك النظرة!‬
Kill me! Please kill me!
‫اقتلني! أرجوك اقتلني!‬
Martin!
‫"مارتن"!‬
I didn't do it! She shot herself!
‫لست أنا من فعل ذلك!‬ ‫هي من أطلقت النار على نفسها!‬
I didn't do it!
‫لست الفاعل!‬
Right? It wasn't me! Right?
‫أليس كذلك؟ لست الفاعل!‬
That's right, isn't it? Amazing! I got it right.
‫كلامي صحيح، أليس كذلك؟ يا للروعة!‬ ‫أصبت كبد الحقيقة.‬
You're wrong.
‫أنت مخطئ.‬
You deserted her.
‫تخليت عنها.‬
You gave her what she wanted.
‫منحتها ما أرادته.‬
-You're wrong. -Then what about your mother?
‫- أنت مخطئ.‬ ‫- ماذا عن أمك إذًا؟‬
Your mother froze to death when you were ten years old, right?
‫تجمدت أمك حتى الموت‬ ‫عندما كنت في العاشرة من عمرك، صحيح؟‬
You deserted your mother too.
‫تخليت عن أمك أيضًا.‬
I'm right about that too! Amazing!
‫أنا محق بشأن ذلك أيضًا! كم هذا مذهل!‬
This is amazing. I can really see these things!
‫كم هذا مذهل. يمكنني كشف الحقائق فعلًا.‬
Every day, you carried your alcoholic mother back home.
‫كنت تحمل أمك الثملة يوميًا إلى البيت.‬
Isn't that right? Your mother would always tell you,
‫أليس كذلك؟ دائمًا ما كانت تقول لك،‬
"Leave me here."
‫"اتركني هنا."‬
Even so, you carried her home every day.
‫مع أنك كنت تحملها إلى البيت يوميًا.‬
But one night…
‫لكن في إحدى الليالي…‬
No, you can't sleep here!
‫لا يمكنك النوم هنا!‬
I'll be fine. Just fine.
‫سأكون بخير.‬
Just leave me here.
‫اتركني هنا فحسب.‬
Wake up!
‫أفيقي!‬
You left her there.
‫تركتها في الشارع.‬
Isn't that right? You left your mother there.
‫أليس كذلك؟ تركت أمك في الشارع.‬
The next day, you were notified that your mother froze to death.
‫أُبلغت في اليوم التالي‬ ‫بأن أمك تجمدت حتى الموت.‬
But this is what you thought then, "It wasn't my fault."
‫لكن هذا ما بدر إلى ذهنك آنذاك،‬ ‫"لم تكن غلطتي.‬
"I only did that because she asked me to leave her there."
‫فعلت ذلك لأنها من طلبت مني‬ ‫أن أتركها في الشارع."‬
You're exactly right. It wasn't your fault.
‫أنت محق تمامًا. لم تكن غلطتك.‬
Both your mother and your drug-addict girlfriend wanted to die.
‫أمك وحبيبتك المدمنة أرادتا أن تموتا.‬
These people wanted to die, so you simply let them.
‫أرادتا أن تموتا، فتركتهما تموتان ببساطة.‬
You didn't do anything wrong. What you did was right.
‫لم تقترف أي خطأ. ما فعلته كان صوابًا.‬
You released them from the misery of life.
‫أرحتهما من بؤس الحياة.‬
Eva too. She wants to die as well.
‫"إيفا" أيضًا. تريد أن تموت.‬
Just then, the devil came.
‫في تلك اللحظة، أتى الشيطان.‬
I didn't look at the devil as we passed by one another.
‫لم أنظر إلى الشيطان‬ ‫في أثناء مرورنا ببعضنا بعضًا.‬
Don't look.
‫لا تنظر.‬
Don't you dare look.
‫إياك أن تجرأ على النظر.‬
I repeated that to myself like a child would.
‫بقيت أكرّر تلك العبارة كما لو كنت طفلًا.‬